La Violetera
Carnations, camellias, violets!
Flowers, sir?
- No, thank you.
The program is good, sir.
Cheer up, take one.
Violets, sir.
- I would love violets!
Thank you, sir. Violets?
They are the flowers of joy!
They only cost one real.
Thank you, sir.
Soledad! Five fresh ones.
- Violets, sir.
Don't say "no"! Ladies like these
deserve flowers like these!
She sells, and we, nothing!
What does she have that I don't?
Violets and she's only 20.
What are you doing here, Lola?
- Shopping.
Where are you spending Christmas?
- Nowhere. - Come to my place.
I'm not sure if I'll make it.
Look how much I have left!
Happy holidays, then!
- Thank you and Happy New Year!
Violets! Violets!
Violets? For your girl, handsome.
- Thank you.
You're welcome.
- Hey, you! We decided you should leave.
Who are "we"?
- All of us.
Let me tell you, I'm not going.